Hello everyone, today we are going to talk about sound transfer and cutting.
This is a common method of processing in women's makeup design.
We divide it into three parts.
The first part is about the principle of sound transfer and elimination.
The second part is about the classification and design applications of sound transfer and elimination.
The third part is about the classification and design applications of cutting.
In the first part, we will talk about the principle of sound transfer and elimination.
It is mainly a matter of the relationship between three-dimensional feeling and sound volume.
We use the primitive form as an example.
Let's say I want to form a cone shape like this.
We all know that the cone shape is made up of a whole circle and a fan shape.
What about the missing corner of the fan shape?
Suppose it is 90 degrees.
No matter where I am at 90 degrees,
whether it is on the left, on the right, or on the right,
no matter where it is,
the degree to which the cone shape is formed after it is sewed should be exactly the same as the first and second corners.
Even if it is a corner of 45 degrees,
or a corner of 20 degrees, or a corner of 70 degrees.
So,
the degree to which the cone shape is formed is exactly the same as the first two corners.
Let's use the square shape as an example.
The top is a three-dimensional effect,
and the bottom is an open picture of the four common cases.
In other words,
if I cut the square shape from somewhere,
it will still be a completely identical shape after it is combined.
The principle of sound transfer is the same as the principle of sound transfer.
In the original form,
our sounds are mainly chest sounds,
dragon sounds,
and so on.
A, B, C, D, E, F sounds, and so on.
In other words,
the sound does not necessarily have to be in the original position.
I can transfer it to any other position.
Next, I will talk about the classification and design application of sound transfer and sales.
The name of the last sound and the method of sound transfer.
Then, the design application,
we will talk about the situation where we want to break the joint,
and the situation where we want to not break the joint.
Next, let's first introduce the name and method of sound transfer of the last sound.
Let's take the front as an example.
Let's talk about the front first.
The front is the name of the various sounds.
We all know that the original sound,
one is A,
which is below B,
and the other is B,
which is below B.
The C sound can be removed directly.
Another very important one is the dragon sound.
In fact, my sound does not necessarily have to be in the original position.
If my sound is not in this position,
and I set the sound to the neck,
then it is called the neck sound.
Set to the shoulder is called the shoulder sound.
Set to the side is called the lower sound.
Set to the front center line is called the front center sound.
The waist is called the waist sound.
This is the name of the structure line corresponding to which position it is in.
The common way of processing the sound transfer is
one is the straight cut method,
and the other is the transfer method.
The straight cut method,
in the past,
we needed to find a piece of paper,
and then take off the original shape,
and then, for example, B sound, I want to merge.
We divide my original shape into the black part and the red part through B sound.
I need to cut off the red part,
and then paste it after adding it,
and then paste the two sides of the sound together.
In this way,
I have completed the elimination of my B sound.
If I want to change the position of a new sound,
for example, I set the position of the new sound to the shoulder sound,
I need to find a piece of paper,
and then take off the original shape,
and then draw the position of the new sound.
The position of the new sound is cut open with scissors,
and then merge the sound of the dragon sound,
and then we draw the structure line smoothly.
The red line is the final structure line.
After drawing,
I drag it onto my paper.
This is the past of B sound.
This is the whole process of practicing B sound.
There is another method,
which is the circular rotation method.
I don't cut another piece of paper.
I draw it on the circle.
For example,
the whole process of my work is still with the shoulder.
Now we still use the shoulder as an example.
Let's say that
this is the circular rotation method.
I want to draw a position of the new sound on the shoulder.
After determining the position of the new sound,
the position of the new sound and the sound of the dragon sound,
I assume that the sound of A does not move.
The position of the new sound and the sound of the dragon sound
divide my original shape into the black part and the red part.
I draw the black part first,
and then draw it on the paper.
After that,
I do not move according to the BP point.
We merge the sound of the dragon sound,
which is to rotate the red part,
and rotate it according to it.
After that,
I draw it again.
Finally,
I draw the position of the new sound.
Of course,
this process is very convenient
if you have a CD later.
However,
if you are a beginner,
you still need to have such a training.
This training is relatively
more easy to understand
if you practice it.
Next,
we will explain in 3D
how to rotate the sound.